I have a lot of time to go.
我有很多时间要去。
Everyone, this is Albert Brooks.
大家好，我是阿尔伯特·布鲁克斯。
I want to do a quick summary of the trading day of 2009, a clock Pacific time.
我想快速总结一下太平洋时间 2009 年的交易日。
And we had on Friday, a small pullback, bold trend day that lasted all day.
我们在周五经历了小幅回调，大胆的趋势日持续了一整天。
And Friday was the last day of the week, last day of the month.
星期五是一周的最后一天，一个月的最后一天。
And on the monthly chart, March was the bicycle bar.
在月度图表上，三月是自行车吧。
We've had lots of bullbars recently, closing in their highs on the monthly chart.
我们最近有很多牛市，收于月度图表上的高位。
Chances are the month is going to go up.
这个月很可能会上涨。
At least a little bit.
至少有一点。
We've been alternating since last year back here.
自去年回到这里以来，我们一直在交替。
And August, it's been bullbear, bullbear, bullbear, then two bears here, two bulls here.
8  月，一直是牛市、牛市、牛市，然后这里有两只熊，这里有两只牛。
But every month has been alternating.
但是每个月都是交替的。
A good looking bicycle bar there here, here, here, here, here,
一个漂亮的自行车吧，这里，这里，这里，这里，这里，
Chances are we're going to go above the high of the bars.
我们很可能会超越最高标准。
So it was likely that we would go above last month's high today or early this week.
因此，我们很可能在今天或本周初突破上个月的高点。
And we went above it today.
我们今天超越了它。
I think we're going up to the August high.
我认为我们将升至 8 月的高点。
I've been saying that for many months now.
我已经说了好几个月了。
I think this is a first leg down from a bi-tomax.
我认为这是 bi-tomax 的第一站。
And I think we'll get a lower high in some kind of a double top.
而且我认为我们会在某种双顶中获得较低的高点。
Maybe with the August high.
也许随着八月的高点。
And then a second leg down.
然后第二条腿下来。
We had a gap up in April, 2021, above 4000 in acceleration of clearly an important price.
我们在 2021 年 4 月跳空，明显高于 4000，这是一个明显重要的价格加速上涨。
And then we've been oscillating around 4000 for 16 months.
然后我们一直在 4000 附近震荡 16 个月。
So clearly an important price.
很明显这是一个重要的价格。
The all time high is important.
历史最高点很重要。
And two important prices often created a third price.
而两个重要的价格往往会产生第三个价格。
A measure moved down from the high to 4000.
一项指标从高位下降至 4000。
Takes us down to around 30, 200, which is below the pre-pandemic high.
使我们下降到 30、200 左右，低于大流行前的高点。
So I think at some point in the next few months we'll form a lower high.
所以我认为在未来几个月的某个时候，我们将形成一个较低的高点。
And we'll get one more leg down, breaking below this low.
我们将再跌一条腿，跌破这个低点。
One of the chances that we just go straight up to a new high.
我们直接升至新高的机会之一。
I don't know, maybe 40%.
我不知道，也许是 40%。
That will just go straight up from the high.
那只会从高处直接上升。
And if we do get up to new high, we've had so many reversals here.
如果我们确实达到了新高，我们已经在这里经历了太多的逆转。
This is training major behavior.
这是训练主要行为。
I think there'll be sellers around that high, a little bit above a little bit below.
我认为在那个高点附近会有卖家，略高于略低于。
So if we do get to new high, I think we'll have a hard time going much above it.
因此，如果我们真的达到新高，我认为我们将很难超越它。
I think we'll get a reversal back down at least to the middle of the developing training range.
我认为我们至少会逆转回到正在发展的训练范围的中间。
On the open today, we had the bullbar closing here in size.
在今天开盘时，我们的牛栏在这里收盘。
When you have a bi-climax day like Friday, there are a couple things that you should know.
当你遇到像周五这样的双高潮日时，你应该知道几件事。
First is there's a 50% chance that you're going to get some follow-through by on the open.
首先，您有 50% 的机会在公开场合获得一些跟进。
And bar one is consistent with that.
K 线一与此一致。
But there's a 75% chance that by the end of the second hour, the market will go sideways to down for at least a couple hours.
但有 75% 的可能性，到第二个小时结束时，市场将横盘整理至少几个小时。
So that is what's likely.
所以这是可能的。
So here we have a bullbar closing there is high, but we know what it will rally you get.
所以这里我们有一个收盘价高的牛栏，但我们知道它会反弹你得到什么。
We'll last five or ten bars probably not much more than that.
我们将持续 5 或 10 个小节，可能仅此而已。
So you have to be prepared to get out fairly quickly if it starts to reverse because we might get a leg all the way down here.
所以你必须准备好在它开始反转时迅速退出，因为我们可能会一直走到这里。
This was an area of agreement on Friday.
这是周五达成的共识。
And if this was not going to far, this would be within reach.
如果这不会走得太远，那将是触手可及的。
The market bulls bought it in the moving average here and here and here and here and here.
市场多头在移动平均线上买入。
And there might just above the moving average here.
并且这里可能略高于移动平均线。
Post below the day, but I think we're going to end up having at least a couple hours of sideways training at some point again starting before the end of the second hour.
在当天发布，但我认为我们最终会在第二个小时结束前的某个时间点再次开始至少几个小时的横向训练。
If you buy above bar one, it's reasonable.
如果您购买高于第一条的价格，那是合理的。
Stop below one, I would trade small and add on as it goes up. For example, you buy above two.
止于 1 以下，我会小幅交易，然后在上涨时加仓。比如你买上面两个。
Now that's the surprisingly strong pair of bars early in the day. It's always in long.
现在这是当天早些时候出人意料的强势金条。它总是很长。
It's thrown it up to buy the closed traders will buy the closed, they'll buy at the market in the buy a bucket.
它被抛出以购买关闭的交易者将购买关闭的交易者，他们将在市场上购买一个桶。
We went a little bit above it and then we had a bear bar closing near it slow.
我们在它上面一点点，然后我们在它附近缓慢关闭了一个熊市K线。
And if you're long for any reason buying one by above two and it goes below three, I would get out because then we have a buy climb axe from yesterday.
而且，如果您出于任何原因以高于 2 的价格买入 1 并且低于 3，我会退出，因为那时我们有昨天的买入攀登斧头。
And a wedge one two three and a good sell signal bar and this could be a bull trap on the open in the chart of a trend down from the higher the day.
楔形一二三和良好的卖出信号条，这可能是趋势图表中开盘时的多头陷阱，从当天的较高点开始下跌。
And so reasonable to exit below three.
所以在三点以下退出是合理的。
And three is a disappointing bar.
三是令人失望的K线。
So some of the bulls who bought the closed of two will try to get off break even if it gets back to the closed of two area.
因此，即使它回到了两个区域的封闭区域，一些购买了两个封闭区域的多头也会尝试下场休息。
And it did bar four.
它确实是第四条。
Or when bar above the closed of two. So instead of bulls getting out bulls bought more.
或者当柱线高于两个收盘价时。因此，多头不是多头出局，而是多头买入。
And that's good. It increases the chances that we'll go higher. This might be a gap. It might lead to a measure move up.
那很好。它增加了我们走得更高的机会。这可能是一个差距。这可能会导致措施上移。
So it's still by the closed traders are still buying at the market.
所以它仍然由关闭的交易商仍在市场上购买。
And then bar five it's a problem. It's a bear bar closing near its low and it's a good size bear bar.
然后是第五条，这是个问题。这是一个收于低点附近的熊市，而且它是一个大小适中的熊市。
It's reasonable to get out below five. You can always buy again if you get a bull bar and then it's a few bars.
低于五点是合理的。如果你得到一个牛栏，然后是几个栏，你总是可以再次购买。
So reasonable to get out of lungs.
离开肺部是合理的。
It's five bars without a pullback. You can argue wedge.
它是 5 根柱线，没有回调。你可以争论楔子。
But five bars without a pullback probably if this is a minor reversal and they'll probably will be buyers not too far below five.
但是，如果这是一个小的逆转，则可能有 5 个没有回调的柱线，并且他们可能会在不低于 5 个柱线的情况下成为买家。
So I would wait for a second cell signal and that goes short blue five.
所以我会等待第二个电池信号，蓝色 5 变短。
Six for the bulls. It's a high one. It's a very strong bull trend. It's a small collectible trend.
六分给公牛队。这是一个很高的。这是一个非常强劲的牛市趋势。这是一个小的收藏趋势。
But it's a bear bar and it's consecutive bear bars. So that is not a very good high one.
但这是一个熊市，而且是连续的熊市。所以这不是一个很好的高点。
Bar three is not a very good high one. It was a size.
K 线三不是一个很好的高。这是一个大小。
Clyde believes pause in the bull trend. But it's still a bicing. About three. They bought about three. They bought about six.
克莱德认为牛市趋势会暂停。但它仍然是一个bicing。大约三个。他们买了大约三个。他们买了大约六个。
When you get bad bicing the bars in a bull trend, it reduces the chances that the bull trend will last all day.
当您在牛市趋势中对 bar 进行不利操作时，牛市趋势持续一整天的可能性就会降低。
It increases the chances that you'll get a reversal at least into a trading range.
它增加了你至少在交易区间内获得逆转的机会。
And that's consistent with what we already know.
这与我们已经知道的一致。
The day after a buy time x day has a 75% chance of having at least a couple hours of sideways to down trading.
买入时间 x 天后的第二天，有 75% 的机会出现至少几个小时的横向下跌交易。
So we're still in a small pullback full trend.
所以我们仍然处于小幅回调的完整趋势中。
But not good viseignal bars that increases the chances that we'll get a reversal before too long.
但不是好的 viseignal bar 会增加我们在不久之后获得逆转的机会。
As I said, maybe five bars ten bars, maybe a little bit more.
正如我所说，也许五小节十小节，也许更多一点。
And now we have another high one. Eight is a pullback in a small pullback bull trend.
现在我们有另一个高的。八是小回调牛市趋势中的回调。
No sign of a top yet. But it's a bear bar.
还没有顶部的迹象。但这是一个熊栏。
So we have a bad bicing of our three, six and now eight.
所以我们的三人、六人和现在八人的双拼很糟糕。
It's still a small pullback bull trend. So the traders will buy for an increase in.
仍然是小幅回调的牛市走势。所以交易者会为增加而买入。
They'll either buy above a high one, a bad bicing of our or they'll buy in a new high.
他们要么买入高于我们的高位，要么买入新高。
So they'll buy for the stop and above that.
所以他们会在止损位及以上止损位买入。
If they don't want to buy above a bear bar, here they'll buy with the stop and above that.
如果他们不想在 Bear Bar 上方买入，他们会在止损点及上方买入。
And so far, the bears are not making money.
到目前为止，空头还没有赚钱。
Limit order bears. If they sold at the five high.
限价单空头。如果他们在五高时卖出。
It had to fall 22 ticks for them to make money. And it did.
他们必须下跌 22 个跳动点才能赚钱。确实如此。
Each line is five points that fell a little bit more than five points.
每条线是五个点，比五个点多一点。
So now limit order bears of starting to make money.
所以现在限价单空头开始赚钱了。
And that increases the chances that the market is transitioning from a strong bull trend into either a weaker bull trend or a training range.
这增加了市场从强劲的牛市趋势转变为较弱的牛市趋势或训练区间的可能性。
And less likely into a bear trend.
并且不太可能进入熊市趋势。
Another bull bar closing near its high. So if traders get off for any reason, they buy again above eight.
另一个多头条收于高点附近。因此，如果交易者出于任何原因下场，他们会在 8 点以上再次买入。
Eleven. You can second bull bars all closing near their highs. So the first reversal down will probably be minor.
十一。您可以将所有收盘价都接近高点的牛市柱作为第二个。因此，第一次向下的反转可能会很小。
You would not short blow 12. But if the stop order bears start making money.
你不会做空 12。但如果止损订单空头开始赚钱。
If the market falls far enough below the low, low bar for bears to make money.
如果市场跌破低点，空头赚钱的低点足够远。
A scalp. Then I would get off. So if it falls 22 ticks below 12.
一个头皮。然后我会下车。因此，如果它跌至 12 以下 22 个刻度。
Stop order bears could make 20 ticks five points. I would get off.
止损订单空头可以使 20 个滴答点变为 5 点。我会下车。
And it's a high one. But as I said, we're probably not going to go up much further.
这是一个很高的。但正如我所说，我们可能不会再上升太多。
So if you buy, I would be really, really quick to get out because as I said, we should be soon having a leg down or at least sideways last thing.
因此，如果你买入，我会非常、非常快地退出，因为正如我所说，我们应该很快就会下跌或至少横盘整理。
At least a couple hours. And this is a training over what bar 13. And I was like down bar.
至少几个小时。这是关于第 13 条的训练。我就像向下的条一样。
But a small bull back bull trend and a. A tight bull channel. So I would not short blow 13.
而是小牛背牛的趋势和一个。紧张的牛市通道。所以我不会做空13。
But if I'm long, I would get out similarly getting out below five. You can always buy again if 14 or 15 is a bull bar.
但如果我做多，我会以同样的方式退出五点以下。如果 14 或 15 是牛栏，您可以随时再次购买。
Instead, 15 14 is a surprisingly big bear bar.
相反，15 14 是一个大得惊人的熊市柱。
And it's a bear surprise and a buy climax. Different ways to look at this as a wish. One, two, three, four, one, two, three or one, two, and then three sub dividing into one, two, three.
这是一个空头惊喜和购买高潮。不同的方式来看待这个愿望。一，二，三，四，一，二，三或一，二，然后三分为一，二，三。
In any case, we know we're going to have a couple hours of sideways to down trading 75% certain.
无论如何，我们知道我们将有几个小时的横盘整理，以 75% 的确定性下跌交易。
And this is a really good looking bear bar. So it's probably the start of a sideways to down move.
这是一个非常好看的熊吧。因此，这可能是横向向下移动的开始。
It could be simply sideways, but we'll probably get at least two legs down after a bear surprise and a buy climax.
它可能只是横盘整理，但在空头意外和买入高潮之后，我们可能至少会下跌两条腿。
So traders will sell the market, sell a lot of long sell into shorts or sell below 14.
所以交易者会卖出市场，大量卖出多头卖出空头或在 14 以下卖出。
13 14. We have consecutive bear bars, one being big and closing near as low. So it's sell the clothes.
13 14.  我们有连续的熊市，一个很大，收盘价接近低点。所以是卖衣服。
It's still probably a minor reversal, but it's sell the clothes. I would not buy at this point.
这仍然可能是一个小的逆转，但它卖掉了衣服。我不会在这一点上购买。
Another bear bar, 15. Now we have three consecutive bear bars, one of them big and closing on as low.
另一个熊市，15。现在我们有三个连续的熊市，其中一个很大，收盘价最低。
We should get a couple of leg sideways to down. So better to be short or flat.
我们应该让几条腿侧身向下。所以最好是短的或扁平的。
And if you're short, you can get out above 13. And now we have another bear bar, 16 closing near as low.
如果你做空，你可以在 13 点上方出场。现在我们有另一个熊市，16 点收盘价接近低点。
So right now, it's a sell the clothes market. We have a closed bullet moving average.
所以现在，这是一个卖衣服的市场。我们有一个封闭的子弹移动平均线。
We've closed the gap between the six low and the free high.
我们已经缩小了六个低点和自由高点之间的差距。
So more and more goals are giving up. We have a small spike pullback channel.
所以越来越多的目标正在放弃。我们有一个小的尖峰回调通道。
We were closing below the bottom of the channel. So it's probably going lower.
我们收于通道底部下方。所以它可能会走低。
So you sell the market or sell as sell the market as soon as 16 closes or you sell at the stop below 16.
因此，您在 16 收盘后立即卖出市场或卖出，或者在 16 下方的止损处卖出。
17 is another very good bar for the bear. So same thing. So the closed sell the market sell for any reason.
17  是熊的另一个非常好的K线。同样的事情。所以关闭卖出市场出于任何原因卖出。
Now, every day has a 90% chance of having at least one swing that goes 40% of an average day is range and it comes from a good signal bar.
现在，每天都有 90% 的机会至少有一次波动幅度达到平均一天的 40%，并且来自良好的信号条。
On the way up, we have a good passing the bar here.
在上山的路上，我们很顺利地通过了这里的栏杆。
So this is going to be the start of a move up.
所以这将是向上移动的开始。
Well, this high is 76 ticks above that. And if the average day is range is 50 points 40% of that is 20 points, which is 80 ticks.
嗯，这个高点比那个高 76 个跳动点。如果平均一天的范围是 50 点，那么其中的 40% 就是 20 点，也就是 80 个跳动点。
And it will have to go 82 ticks above one for the bulls to make 20 points profit.
多头必须高于 1 点 82 点才能获利 20 点。
And this is 76 ticks above. So the bulls are born above one.
这是上面的 76 个跳动点。所以多头出生在一个之上。
So the reason that this would be a swing trade they gave up on 14. 14 is a really good bear bar and a good candidate for the sort of a swing down.
因此，这将是他们在 14 点放弃的摇摆交易的原因。14 是一个非常好的熊市，并且是那种向下摆动的很好的候选者。
So it's reasonable to sell below 14 on a stop and try to get out 80 ticks below your entry price.
因此，在 14 点以下止损卖出并尝试以低于入场价 80 个跳动点的价格卖出是合理的。
So you enter one tick below 14. You need 80 ticks to make your 20 points.
因此，您在 14 以下输入一个跳动点。您需要 80 个跳动点才能获得 20 分。
And if you're exiting with a limit order 80 ticks below your entry, it has to go one more tick. So you enter one tick below 14.
如果您以低于入场价 80 个跳动点的限价单离场，则它必须再走一个跳动点。所以你在 14 以下输入一个刻度。
It has to fall 81 ticks more for you to exit with 20 points.
它必须再下跌 81 个跳动点，您才能以 20 点退出。
So it has to fall 82 ticks below 14. So a lot of bulls will place limit orders to get out.
所以它必须跌到 14 以下 82 个跳动点。所以很多多头会下限价单来退出。
A lot of bearish will place limit orders to get out at 82 ticks below it's quality.
许多看跌者会下限价单，以低于其质量 82 个跳动点离场。
And right now it's selling a close and looking good. It's still selling markets sell the close. If you traded small, you can add on here and on here and on here.
现在它卖得很好，看起来不错。它仍在卖出市场卖出收盘价。如果你的交易量很小，你可以在这里、这里和这里添加。
We make it some bounce around the earlier flow of the day.
我们让它在当天早些时候的流程中有所反弹。
The bulls are hoping that we get a double bottom in a rally, but this is so strong to major bearish surprise at this point.
多头希望我们在反弹中获得双底，但这对目前的主要看跌意外来说是如此强烈。
A bearish surprise increases the chances that you get at least a small second leg sidewester down.
一个看跌的惊喜增加了你至少得到一个小的第二腿侧西的机会。
A major bear surprise increases the chances that the day will either be a training wage day or a bear friend day.
一个重大的熊惊喜增加了这一天成为培训工资日或熊朋友日的机会。
So this could be a spike and then we could bounce and get a channel down.
所以这可能是一个尖峰，然后我们可以反弹并使通道下降。
Or it could be a cell climb axe and we could rally back up to the high and then just go sideways all day.
或者它可能是一个细胞爬升斧，我们可以反弹回高点，然后整天横盘整理。
A doggie bar in a cell climb axe. That is a neutral bar.
牢房攀爬斧中的小狗栏。那是一个中立的K线。
The bulls equal the bears pretty close to being equal. So it's probably getting close to the end of the selling.
多头与空头相当接近。所以它可能接近销售结束。
And as I said, there'll be bulls buying back. There'll be bears buying back short.
正如我所说，会有多头回购。会有空头回购空头。
82 ticks below 14. The bulls know that. So bulls will start scaling into longs betting that we'll get a bounce pretty soon.
82  点低于 14。多头知道这一点。因此多头将开始扩大多头押注我们很快就会反弹。
Maybe a bounce to 50% of the way up.
也许会反弹到上涨的 50%。
Another cell to close bar. But a tail. And after that doggie bar. And we're getting pretty close to 82 ticks below 14.
关闭另一个单元格吧。而是一条尾巴。在那个小狗K线之后。我们已经非常接近 14 以下的 82 个刻度。
So I think it's probably better not to sell the clothes.
所以我认为最好不要卖衣服。
Even though arguably you could sell the clothes. I would wait.
即使可以说你可以卖衣服。我会等。
And then 20. I think we're 76 that ticks down from the high.
然后是 20。我认为我们是 76，从高点开始下降。
Just like this high was 76 ticks about that. This low is 76 below the selling more 14.
就像这个高点大约是 76 个跳动点。这个低点比卖多 14 低 76。
Probably sellers above 21. But we're right at a profit taking area. So I don't want to short. And I don't want to buy the first one.
可能是 21 岁以上的卖家。但我们正处于获利回吐区域。所以我不想做空。我不想买第一个。
Russel up. And then you get 22. It's a pretty good bull bar closing near its high.
拉塞尔起来。然后你得到 22。这是一个非常好的牛市柱，收盘价接近其高点。
A bull surprise. Probably will lead to at least a small second leg up.
公牛惊喜。大概会导致至少小的第二回合上涨。
And might go to 50% up, which is this pink line.
并且可能会上涨 50%，也就是这条粉线。
And it might test you at least to the moving average. And I'll probably get at least a couple legs. I wish to up.
它可能至少会测试你的移动平均线。我可能至少会得到几条腿。我想起来。
So I'd wait to sell. And for the bull. They can argue it's a failed breakout below the load of the day.
所以我等着卖。对于公牛。他们可以争辩说这是在当天负载下的一次失败突破。
So in computer soils feet as a lower and moved double bottom with one.
因此，在计算机土壤脚作为一个较低的移动双底与一个。
Others you'll see it as a higher and lower double bottom with 77.
在其他情况下，您会将其视为 77 的上下双底。
If you buy, I would use a WI stop like 10.15 or 20 points down in scale and lower.
如果你买入，我会使用 WI 止损，比如 10.15 或 20 点的规模和更低。
And most traders will mess that up. So most traders are better off not scaling in. So if you buy.
大多数交易者都会把它搞砸。所以大多数交易者最好不要扩大规模。所以如果你买了。
You put a stop load 21. And hope that it's the start of the swing.
你放了一个停止负载 21。希望这是摆动的开始。
It's probably the start of a training range. It could be a brief training range and we'll form a bear flag and then get down to 80 to 6 below 14.
这可能是训练场的开始。这可能是一个简短的训练范围，我们将形成一个熊旗，然后将 80 比 6 降至 14 以下。
Or it could go up 20 to 30 bars and then try to go down later in the day.
或者它可能会上涨 20 到 30 条，然后在当天晚些时候尝试下跌。
Okay. Now we have five bars, six bars up without a pull there.
好的。现在我们有五个杆，六个杆没有拉动。
So probably buyers below 26. But we're getting small bars. A lot of overlap between the bars.
所以可能是 26 岁以下的买家。但我们得到的是小金条。条之间有很多重叠。
This is probably not going to go very far up. It looks like limit water trading bears will sell above things. So bears will sell the 25 high and 5. higher or the start to sell 5. higher.
这可能不会走得太远。看起来限水交易空头会卖出以上东西。所以空头将卖出 25 高点和 5. 高点或开始卖出 5. 高点。
Because we're probably going up to yesterday's high. So probably better not to sell the 26 high. And you know at this point that we're probably going up here maybe 50% pull back.
因为我们可能会涨到昨天的高点。所以最好不要卖出 26 高点。你知道在这一点上我们可能会上涨 50%。
So if you're looking to sell with limit orders, I would sell in this area, not right here. And bulls. It's six bars without a pull back. We should get a second leg up after 22 so they can buy 26.
所以如果你想用限价单卖出，我会在这个区域卖出，而不是在这里。和公牛。这是六个K线，没有拉回。我们应该在 22 之后获得第二条腿，以便他们可以购买 26。
Or they can wait for a good spot in 3 by. To me this looks like the early part of a tight training range.
或者他们可以等待 3 by 的好位置。对我来说，这看起来像是紧张训练范围的早期部分。
We have outside up 28, but small bar of cyglies bars. It looks like more limit order trading sellers will sell above things that goes up and they'll buy below things as it goes down.
我们外面有 28 个，但 cyglies K线的小K线。看起来更多的限价订单交易卖家会在上涨的东西上方卖出，而在价格下跌时他们会在下方买入。
Okay, this is right around 9 o'clock, which is when I stopped the chat room. And I said that we should reach about 50% retracement that my leads to some profit taking.
好的，现在是 9 点左右，也就是我停止聊天室的时候。我说我们应该达到大约 50% 的回撤位，我的回撤位会导致一些获利了结。
Maybe we'll come down to the 28 low. Maybe we'll get down to 76 ticks below this. And it's possible that this is the start of another.
也许我们会跌至 28 美元的低点。也许我们会跌至低于此水平的 76 个跳动点。这可能是另一个的开始。
If you're going to go to the right now at this point, I think it's likely that we're going to go sideways soon. But sometimes when you have a cell climb, actually in the day, you reverse up in a small pull back, but we'll try and just keep going up.
如果你现在要向右转，我认为我们很快就会横向移动。但有时当你有一个细胞爬升时，实际上是在白天，你会在一个小的回撤中逆转，但我们会尝试并继续上升。
Like this, sometimes here, we're not a little bit, you know, we had this big big cell climb next and we had a big bull bar closing in and it's high and we just drifted up. When you get that, usually it does not go far above the earlier high. Sometimes it goes above the high, sometimes it does not.
就像这样，有时在这里，我们不是一点点，你知道，接下来我们有一个大的大单元攀登，我们有一个大的牛栏正在关闭，它很高，我们只是向上漂移。当你得到它时，通常它不会远高于早期的高点。有时它会超过最高点，有时不会。
But sometimes when you have these big big cell climb access on the open and a reversal, they can just last all day in a small pull back bull trend. And that's what today did it went back all the way up to the high.
但有时，当你在开盘和反转中获得这些大的大细胞攀升通道时，它们可能会在一个小的回调牛市趋势中持续一整天。这就是今天所做的，它一直回到高位。
But at this point, it's a small pull back bull trend. It's by the market by the closed, but we're around 50% after a pretty dramatic move. So I think you'll start getting limit order bear selling. I would not sell with the stop and a small pull back bull trend.
但在这一点上，这是一个小幅回调的牛市趋势。收盘时按市场计算，但在经历了相当大的变动后，我们的比例约为 50%。所以我认为你会开始接受限价单熊市卖出。我不会在止损和小幅回调牛市趋势时卖出。
I'd like to start with these on bear bars, we don't have yet. And I don't want to be buying here because this is strong enough to get a second leg sideways to down and now we're at a 50% retracement in rat yesterday's high. So there will be some sellers here.
我想从熊栏上的这些开始，我们还没有。而且我不想在这里买入，因为它的强度足以让第二条腿横盘向下，现在我们处于昨天高点的 50% 回撤位。所以这里会有一些卖家。
I think we're going to have a third-ing range of high one above 36. I'm not going to buy it. Looks like a tight training range. And then you can fail break off below a double bottom, double bottom 3537.
我认为我们将有一个高于 36 的第三个范围。我不打算买它。看起来像一个紧凑的训练场。然后你可能无法突破双底，双底 3537。
I think you can buy it, but if you buy it, you need a wide stop because it may drift back down to the most recent higher low gear.
我认为你可以买它，但如果你买它，你需要一个广泛的止损，因为它可能会回落到最近的较高低档。
Well, we get all the way down here. I think it's less certain that we've rallied for about an hour in a very tight channel. So we may just stay sideways all day or we may get up here. So it's unclear.
好吧，我们一直走到这里。我认为不太确定我们已经在一个非常紧张的通道中反弹了大约一个小时。所以我们可能整天都呆在一边，或者我们可能会站起来。所以不清楚。
If we get down here, there'll be buyers this may continue in a small pull back bull trend up here, but it's unlikely to go much above. And you can see that's what happened. 21 is a bad bison in the bar. So some bear are sold the 21 high.
如果我们跌到这里，就会有买家，这可能会在此处继续出现小幅回调的牛市趋势，但不太可能高出太多。你可以看到这就是发生的事情。 21 是K线里的坏野牛。所以一些空头卖出了 21 高点。
And they waited for bear bars closing the other ones and then they sold more like maybe below a 39 and they know that's an 80% chance that they can avoid loss, but they'll be able to get out at least break even.
他们等待熊线关闭其他的，然后他们卖得更像可能低于 39，他们知道他们有 80% 的机会可以避免损失，但他们至少能够实现收支平衡。
So ignore that, let me get hurt at that. The structure, get hurt at that. So for scaling bears if they sold the 21 high and then sold more 5.5 or 10.15 points higher or they simply waited for bear bar closing here. It's low and then sold below it. So you sell one take a low 39.
所以忽略它，让我为此受到伤害。结构，受到伤害。因此，对于空头来说，如果他们卖出 21 高点，然后再高出 5.5 或 10.15 点，或者他们只是等待熊市收盘。它很低，然后在其下方卖出。所以你卖出一个低价 39。
There's an 80% chance it's going to go to the midpoint of your two cells. First, I'll here at the 21 high and the second, I'll below 39.
它有 80% 的可能性会到达两个单元格的中点。首先，我会在 21 点高位，其次，我会低于 39 点。
80% chance that'll go to the midpoint and that would allow you to get out break even. So and it did and it got down there and reversed up strongly. And this is mostly bears trying to get out break even on their trade.
80%  的机会会到达中点，这将使您实现收支平衡。所以它做到了，它在那里下降并强烈逆转。这主要是空头试图在交易中实现收支平衡。
And bulls know bears would do that so you have bulls buying as well and you have bulls foking for a double bottom here. And then we just went up and a small collect bulls try actually went down a little bit more and then up.
多头知道空头会那样做，所以你也有多头买进，多头在这里寻找双底。然后我们就上升了，一个小的收集公牛尝试实际上下降了一点然后上升了。
And then back in like down tough to sell after that and then here you can or a lower load of a bottom you can call it a break up below this double bottom. Not really good buy but once you start to get bull bars closing in the house, maybe here or here.
然后像向下一样很难卖出，然后在这里你可以或较低的底部负荷你可以称之为低于这个双底的突破。不太好买，但一旦你开始让牛栏在房子里关闭，也许在这里或这里。
It's a buy now when you start to get to a three bull bars it's a buy. Now when you start to get big bull bars closing in the other house breaking above a lower high it's a buy. So for the bears they have a minor lower high here they have a major lower high here.
当您开始到达三个牛栏时，现在就买入。现在，当您开始在另一个房子中收盘时突破较低的高点，这就是买入。因此，对于空头来说，这里有一个较低的小高点，这里有一个较低的主要高点。
If we get above that maybe we'll walk for a mission move based upon the trading range and get up through the high of the day.
如果我们超过这一点，我们可能会根据交易区间走上一个任务移动，并通过当天的高点起床。
And here we have consecutive bull bars with decent bodies with at least one of them closing their at high this is a break up above this so we're going up for measuring move probably.
在这里，我们有连续的牛市K线，身体不错，其中至少有一个在高位收盘，这是一个高于此的突破，所以我们可能会上涨以衡量走势。
It could be a measure move based upon height of this range or it could be a measure move based upon the entire leg up to the breakout point.
它可以是基于此范围高度的测量移动，也可以是基于直到突破点的整个腿的测量移动。
Which gets us near the high of the day and that's in fact where we ended up and one other point about where we ended up at the end of the day.
这让我们接近当天的高点，这实际上是我们结束的地方以及关于我们在一天结束时结束的地方的另一点。
This high is this is a reasonable buy just like that was a reasonable buy we went 70 six ticks not 82.
这个高是一个合理的买入，就像那个是一个合理的买入，我们去了 70 六点而不是 82。
This was a reasonable sell we fell 76 not 82 have a person bought here they were able to make four points I think it went up exactly 82 ticks right here.
这是一个合理的卖出价，我们下跌了 76 点而不是 82 点，有人在这里买入，他们能够赚到 4 个点，我认为它在这里上涨了 82 个跳动点。
It would be hard to hold one so if you bought that I think you can get up a little that or that but you could buy again over here or over here hoping that it goes up to 82 ticks above that which it did or you could buy above this bull bar closing in at high.
很难持有一个，所以如果你买了那个，我认为你可以上涨一点，但你可以在这里或在这里再次购买，希望它比它所做的高出 82 个跳动点，或者你可以买高于此牛市收盘价。
If you want higher probability you buy above this or you buy above that looking for some kind of a measure move up.
如果你想要更高的概率，你可以在这个之上购买，或者你在那个之上购买，以寻找某种向上的衡量标准。
Okay and that is all hope everybody had a good day and I hope you found this helpful.
好的，这就是所有希望每个人都有美好的一天，我希望你发现这有帮助。